{
    "id": "9125e28b0c6a4ae4a4929f61f0fa8123",
    "title": "Sentence Correction Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy looked ........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pail",
                "pale"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8f1e2a03a6f4436b9a0631e9b414173"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack and Jill went up the hill to fetch a ............................. of water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pail",
                "pale"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "25cf2294a99141e888388d5f5b7ecd41"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to ..........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "London",
                "the London"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa04581d57b64b2b8880f6ebd0892ca1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ........................... finished their homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37d08458cd1b4b72b694dd98d3ac3d78"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog licked ......................... baby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it's",
                "its"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "78bcde1eab514d33b215cc1f45bf2e45"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................... raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Its",
                "It's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6a55fac9d0845f5814a5ac5c02d2a31"
        },
        {
            "question": "Letâ€™s go .................... train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29e6086fc2c4415ea2e2c8e70b259ea8"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ....................... the cake in the oven.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "baked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f63b7d709294e139fb12a5ab358be0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie was ..........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "disinteresting",
                "uninteresting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0bf065305586468d8dc143c7e0731ac0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ....................... his wife to look after their children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "told to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7413b3045ab04143b6c1441fba47db4c"
        }
    ]
}